Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nhi-nguyen-ds (LinkedIn)
nhim.design/ (Portfolio)
anzi.com.vn/ (Company)
www.facebook.com/nhinguyen.ds
(Personal)

Top Skills

Research

Team Leadership

Teamwork

Nhi Nguyen

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Quận Bình Tân, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Portfolio: ♦ https://www.behance.net/nhids ♦ I'm looking for freelancer, parttime, remote jobs about UI UX and graphic design.

I'm Nhi form HCMC, Vietnam.

I'm a UI/UX/Graphic designer for almost 5 years. Currently working in web, app and graphical project.

Something about me: Thinking, ambitious, introverted, quiet, strict, flexible, perfectionism, humorous,...

NGUYEN NHI

yennhinguyen102@gmail.com nhi.nguyen995 (Skype) 0349063214 (SMS/Zalo/Viber) http://nhim.design/

Thank you!

Experience

Freelancer

Freelancer UI, UX, GRAPHIC Designer February 2015 - Present (10 years 2 months)

Hồ Chí Minh, Việt Nam

PatientHoney
Head Designer
December 2019 - Present (5 years 4 months)
United States

SB&P LOGISTICS

Senior Designer

November 2019 - Present (5 years 5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

BookOke Senior UI/UX, Graphic Designer August 2015 - October 2019 (4 years 3 months) Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

Education

FPT-Arena Multimedia
Bachelors, Graphic Design · (2013 - 2016)